https://www.soberforever.net/privacypolicy.cfm

For The Family
The Alternative To...
Terms and Conditions
The Saint Jude Retreats & The Freedom Model Program options do not provide services requiring certification by the New York State Office of Alcoholism and Substance Abuse Services. We are regulated by the NYS Department of Health, our instructors are certified by the NYS Department of Education, and our not-for-profit status is regulated by the NYS Charities Bureau and NYS Attorney General's Office.
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which The Saint Jude Retreats collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.soberforever.net website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by The Saint Jude Retreats.
It is a pleasure to offer you this website, and the knowledge it brings forth.
By using this website, you willingly agree to the terms and conditions mandated by The Saint Jude Retreats.
Please take careful review of the following terms and conditions stated below, as well as the Privacy Policy to ensure your complete confidential relationship with The Saint Jude Retreats, in respect to this website.
These terms and conditions clearly stated constitute the entire and sole agreement between yourself and The Saint Jude Retreats.
It overrides any prior agreements that may or may not have been in place.
All content, material, data, research, photos, audio, visual, and text are protected under this agreement, in respect to this website.
The Saint Jude Retreats is aware of the risks involved with internet use.
There are no guarantees that all information submitted will remain untouched by any illegitimate third party. Additionally, The Saint Jude Retreats will not be held liable if you or any other party unlawfully uses your email, or releases confidential information not intentionally disclosed by The Saint Jude Retreats.
These terms and conditions are subject to change at any given time.
Please note that by your use of this website, you agree to all terms and conditions upon any changes that occur.
If you have any questions or concerns related to this website, the Terms and Conditions, or the Privacy Policy please contact us.
TRADEMARK
The following are registered trademarks of Baldwin Research Institute, Inc., and are protected by the international property law: The Freedom Model, Saint Jude Retreats, the Jude Thaddeus Program, the Jude Thaddeus Home Program, The Freedom Model, and the Cognitive Behavioral Learning Model.
CONTENT
Baldwin Research Institute claims full ownership of all web pages, materials, data, and information provided on this website. Use of the materials and information provided on this website are restricted to personal use only.
Web pages may be printed for personal use.
But the reselling, redistributing, rewriting, modification, or use for any other commercial purpose is explicitly prohibited.
All content, materials, and information provided and displayed on this website are copyrighted, with all rights reserved to The Saint Jude Retreats.
THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS APPLY TO ONLY THE SAINT JUDE RETREATS WEBSITE.
NOTHING OF THIS AGREEMENT PERTAINS TO ANYTHING OFF THIS WEBSITE.
PRIVACY POLICY
Any personal information submitted by you and collected by The Saint Jude Retreats is per your own request.
We do not collect information without your willingness and consent.
Any contact from The Saint Jude Retreats only occurs with your prior knowledge and consent.
Any information submitted is kept confidential and only used for your purpose at The Saint Jude Retreats.
All Information submitted and collected is used for the sole purpose to benefit your experience with the The Saint Jude Retreats and this website.
Information is only collected per your submission, and correspondence with one of our professionals is based upon your request.
E-MAIL AND CONTACT REQUEST
All emails submitted to The Saint Jude Retreats, via this website, are strictly confidential. The Saint Jude Retreats will not release, trade, or sell any personal information to any third party organization.
Information submitted is held in a specific data base and only used for your purpose with The Saint Jude Retreats.
If you submit emails to The Saint Jude Retreats, please be aware of the risks that can be involved with online communication.
Secure connections may not always be available, and the threat of unauthorized third party access is possible.
Emails are submitted to The Saint Jude Retreats, via this website.
No minimum information is required in order to submit an email.
Visitors to this Web site can decide if they want to receive more information from The Saint Jude Retreats in order to help them directly or a family member. Should visitors decide to send an e-mail via any of the contact forms on this site, their information will be stored in a data base (with access only by The Saint Jude Retreats Reservations Department) IF THE VISITIORS DECIDES TO REMOVE THEIR INFORMATION FROM THE DATA BASE PLEASE CALL OUR TOLL FREE NUMBER AT 888.424.2626 or BY MAIL AT 9 MARKET STREET SUITE 4, AMSTERDAM, NY 12010 ATTN: Reservations Department. they receive will include instructions on how to be removed from The Home Recovery Program promotional e-mail list. If you continue receiving email after opting out, please contact us using the online contact form or by phone at (518) 842-3052 Ext 211.
A contact request form is accessible through this website and whatever method of contact is best can be chosen on the form.
All contact information is kept confidential in our data bases, and only used for your purpose with The Saint Jude Retreats.
THIRD PARTY LINKS
AThere is some information from outside sources available to view through this website.
It is not affiliated with, nor is it a liability to The Saint Jude Retreats or any of our trademarks.
These third party sources and references are for more information regarding topics, research, data, or people discussed on part of this website.
No information submitted to the Saint Jude Retreats will be disclosed to any of these third party sources.
Please note that The Saint Jude Retreats is not liable for any of the content, activity, terms and services, or privacy policy of these third parties.
THIS PRIVACY POLICY PERTAINS ONLY TO INFORMATION ON, AND INFORMATION SUBMITTED TO THE ST. JUDE RETREAT'S WEBSITE.
THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT PERTAIN TO ANY INFORMATION SUBMITTED AND COLLECTED OFF OF THIS WEBSITE.
Call Today - We Can Help YouYour Confidentiality is Guaranteed
Americas #1 NON 12 Step Drug and Alcohol Rehab Centers Alternative
America's Non 12 Step Program
Get Help Now
Call Today We Can Help You
Your confidentiality is guaranteed.
888-424-2626
